Guys, this is a question on how to make
learning systems at home. This is a landing
system that I purchased. I don't know
what its use is. You can blend it
very well with your pencil setting.
Ghee. To make it,
you need this pack copy which is
used for power in tuition. I
practice in it in my drawing room. Okay, so tear out
a page from it. After that,
apply a little water on your hand and
fold the paper in one direction.
[Music]
And just like you roll out a roti, you have to
grease the paper until your paper is
completely set. After this,
apply fevicol on the end of the paper so that your
paper does not open later. Cut its leaf in the middle. Once cut,
you will have to send it to the centre to
get a slightly round shape. So guys, I will
use it and show you how it works. If you have got
any help from many places, then
like it and if you are new to the channel, then
quickly subscribe so that such
interesting videos keep coming on my channel. So, see you
in the next video. Bye.